{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396427313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396427312"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396430604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396430604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396435105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396435105"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396437896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396437896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396442053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396442053"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396445246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396445245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396449710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396449710"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396452202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396452202"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396455891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396455890"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396458998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396458998"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396464940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396464940"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396466716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396466715"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396469994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396469994"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396478984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396478984"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396481913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396481913"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396489017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396489017"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396490946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396490946"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396494849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396494848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396497666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396497666"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396502371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396502371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396504347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396504346"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 2738cad3-274e-4fdb-8c57-8f5af9fccef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396515055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396515055"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396515279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396515279"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396516255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396516254"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396517540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396517540"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396520451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396520450"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396521303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396521303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396521626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396521626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396522872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396522872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396526428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396526428"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396527422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396527422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396527684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396527683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396528639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396528638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396531511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396531510"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396532556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396532556"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396533039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396533038"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396537594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396537593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396537674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396537674"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a9b593d6-cced-42c4-bc68-a4f2b6d077c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396546448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396546448"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396551497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396551497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396556248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396556248"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-a-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396559887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396559887"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396563200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396563200"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396566120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396566120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396569724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396569724"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396572584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396572584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396576026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396576026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-o-e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396578936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396578936"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-i-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396582507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396582507"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396587340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396587340"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee1e1a75-efae-4176-8d6e-d4a9d1f0aa15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396613781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396613781"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396614380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396614379"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396618796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396618796"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396623161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396623161"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396626245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396626245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396632156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396632156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396634352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396634352"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396635291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396635291"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396638520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396638520"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396641416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396641416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396645807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396645807"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396648088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396648088"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396652480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396652479"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396652676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396652676"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396657401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396657401"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396661493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396661492"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396663551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396663551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396669967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396669967"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396676050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396676050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396680920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396680920"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396683441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396683441"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396684098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396684097"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396685174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396685174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396685397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396685397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" e4145a09-f7fa-422f-967d-871570549059"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396707796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396707795"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_u_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396714421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396714421"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396721072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396721072"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396727718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396727718"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396734318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396734318"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396741768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396741768"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396748419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396748418"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_e_o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396755045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396755045"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_e"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396761700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396761700"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396769156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396769156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396779305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396779305"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396785491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396785490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_a_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396786405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396786404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_i_a_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396793794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396793794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_i_a_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396801070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396801070"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 8ed7c7bf-e511-463f-8e07-7693b40f3fea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_i_a_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396811199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396811199"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" b1e40ebb-5a6a-4b3a-8dce-3099a09bfe88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396816742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396816742"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" b1e40ebb-5a6a-4b3a-8dce-3099a09bfe88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396822289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396822288"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" b1e40ebb-5a6a-4b3a-8dce-3099a09bfe88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396830122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396830122"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" b1e40ebb-5a6a-4b3a-8dce-3099a09bfe88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396834840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396834840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" b1e40ebb-5a6a-4b3a-8dce-3099a09bfe88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396842848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396842848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4a6ebf36-6a95-480b-817b-6217f5f42220"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396853235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396853235"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4a6ebf36-6a95-480b-817b-6217f5f42220"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396859455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396859454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4a6ebf36-6a95-480b-817b-6217f5f42220"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396889010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396889009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396913915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396913915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396933361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396933361"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396935686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396935686"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396958124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396958124"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396977512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396977512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548396980487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548396980487"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397026575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397026574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397026651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397026651"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397033764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397033764"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 582d3a01-f594-4efc-b244-a77900edc1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397045467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397045467"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397047295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397047295"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397053845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397053845"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397064240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397064239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397072840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397072840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397089699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397089698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397095428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397095427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397107576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397107575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 6d8561e8-c4e9-4514-a00a-3c52e6b90e78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397126677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397126676"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397135138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397135137"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397136763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397136763"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397145918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397145918"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397147506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397147505"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397152941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397152941"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397154982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397154981"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397155087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397155087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 349e44e0-3a11-47ee-b409-ef318214abf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397164822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397164822"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397170590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397170590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397176134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397176134"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397181810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397181809"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397188675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397188675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397194478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397194478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397196868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397196867"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" beace331-0f30-4238-8365-33d6f2c304ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397206607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397206606"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397207360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397207359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397208193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397208192"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397209074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397209074"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397209669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397209669"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397210423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397210422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397212951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397212951"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397213476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397213476"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397214336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397214335"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397215301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397215301"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397215862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397215861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397216577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397216576"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397219473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397219473"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397220200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397220200"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397220314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397220314"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397221749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397221746"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397222139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397222138"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397222178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397222177"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397225864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397225863"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397226534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397226533"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397227465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397227465"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397228350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397228349"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397228570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397228570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397228612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397228612"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397232923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397232922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397233547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397233547"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397233631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397233631"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397234418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397234417"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397235346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397235346"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397236576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397236575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397238845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397238844"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397239552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397239552"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397239828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397239828"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397240907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397240907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397241466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397241465"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397241516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397241516"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397245937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397245937"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397246545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397246544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397247370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397247370"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397247506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397247506"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397248264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397248264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397249593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397249593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397252023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397252022"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397252532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397252531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397253545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397253544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397254422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397254421"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397255042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397255042"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397255847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397255847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397258926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397258926"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397260890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397260890"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397261133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397261133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397261517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397261517"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397261720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397261720"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397262610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397262610"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397265529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397265529"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397266002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397266002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397267012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397267009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397267201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397267201"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397268466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397268465"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397269277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397269277"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397271940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397271939"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397272057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397272057"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 16a76ef6-78b1-40b9-a433-6ec7e4d78719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397302124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397302124"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_vile-pale-jinsi-ndege"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" jinsi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397304954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397304954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_vile-pale-jinsi-ndege"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" pale"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397307861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397307861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_vile-pale-jinsi-ndege"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397310551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397310551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_vile-pale-jinsi-ndege"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397339316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397339316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuruka_tule-si-kunguru-kuruka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kuruka"," userResponse":" kuruka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397358017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397358015"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta_helikopta-ulimwengu-mgonjwa-bure"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" helikopta"," userResponse":" ulimwengu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397361187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397361187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta_helikopta-ulimwengu-mgonjwa-bure"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" helikopta"," userResponse":" mgonjwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397366274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397366274"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta_helikopta-ulimwengu-mgonjwa-bure"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" helikopta"," userResponse":" bure"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397369130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397369130"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta_helikopta-ulimwengu-mgonjwa-bure"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" helikopta"," userResponse":" helikopta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397388034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397388034"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sawa_huu-je-sawa-njoo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sawa"," userResponse":" njoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397391275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397391275"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sawa_huu-je-sawa-njoo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sawa"," userResponse":" sawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397399890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397399890"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sawa_huu-je-sawa-njoo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397399985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397399985"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397405954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397405954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" fbafe5dc-09bf-4aa3-9993-bf7af57bffbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397417652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397417652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397419234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397419234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397419654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397419654"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397419936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397419936"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397420261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397420261"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397420543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397420543"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397422766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397422766"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397427212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397427212"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397428615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397428615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 623cf234-f298-4d7b-ae0e-7099bfa0de64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397438572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397438571"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397439323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397439323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397440154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397440153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397441037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397441037"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397441638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397441638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397441896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397441895"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397441972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397441972"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" bacb92d2-8aec-4054-8448-070279ed648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397457777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397457777"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397458059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397458059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397458872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397458871"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397458975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397458975"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397459833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397459833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397460280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397460280"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397461317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397461316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397462461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397462461"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397462816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397462816"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397463400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397463400"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397464274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397464274"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397467500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397467500"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397468150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397468149"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397468709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397468709"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397469078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397469078"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397469968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397469968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397470775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397470775"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397471372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397471371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397472013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397472012"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397472814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397472814"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397473236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397473236"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397474080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397474079"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397474616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397474616"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397475500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397475500"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397476371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397476370"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397479555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397479553"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397480275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397480275"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397481241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397481241"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397481959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397481958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397482639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397482639"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397483049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397483049"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397483278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397483277"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397483742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397483742"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKA"," userResponse":" MWAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397484458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397484458"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397487088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397487087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397488141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397488141"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397488968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397488968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397489488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397489488"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397489650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397489650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397490258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397490258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397491020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397491020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397494284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397494284"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397494573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397494573"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397495536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397495536"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397496229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397496228"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397497742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397497741"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" WALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397498784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397498783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397499118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397499118"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397500087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397500087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397502815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397502815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397503951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397503950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKONDA"," userResponse":" AMEKONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397504190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397504190"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397504659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397504659"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397505475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397505475"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397508620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397508620"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397509049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397509049"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397509656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397509655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397510601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397510600"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397511567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397511567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397512170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397512169"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397512654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397512654"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397513288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397513288"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFYA"," userResponse":" AFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397516080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397516080"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397516856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397516855"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397517102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397517101"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397517815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397517814"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397518678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397518678"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397519502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397519502"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397520385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397520385"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397523401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397523401"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397524115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397524115"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397524742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397524741"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397525176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397525176"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397525334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397525333"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397525807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397525807"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397526612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397526612"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397527838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397527838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397528103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397528103"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITUA"," userResponse":" ILITUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397529302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397529302"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397529373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397529373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397530196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397530195"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397533212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397533211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397533486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397533485"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397534400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397534400"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397535043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397535043"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397536677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397536677"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" WALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397537201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397537201"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397537715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397537715"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397540186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397540186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397540289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397540289"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397541293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397541293"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397542348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397542347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397542522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397542522"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397543096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397543096"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397544070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397544070"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ALIFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397544784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397544784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397545441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397545441"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397546236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397546236"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397549070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397549070"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397549755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397549755"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397550798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397550798"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397551502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397551502"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397552437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397552437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397555182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397555181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397555384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397555384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397555978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397555977"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397556142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397556142"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397556626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397556626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397557179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397557179"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397559882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397559881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397560761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397560761"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMLISHA"," userResponse":" ALIMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397561354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397561354"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397562098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397562098"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397562682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397562681"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397565808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397565808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397565972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397565971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397566545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397566544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397567398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397567398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397567553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397567553"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397568557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397568557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397569121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397569121"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397572129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397572123"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKISHWA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397572837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397572837"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397573842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397573838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397574361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397574360"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397575142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397575142"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBWA"," userResponse":" KUBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397575669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397575669"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397576300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397576299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397577138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397577138"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397579653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397579652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397579893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397579892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397580496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397580496"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397580663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397580663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397581280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397581280"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397581868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397581868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397584774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397584774"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397585847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397585847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397586604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397586604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397589359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397589358"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397589972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397589972"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397590144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397590144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397590838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397590838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397591122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397591122"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397591874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397591874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENKARE"," userResponse":" ENKARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397593158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397593158"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" AMBAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397593753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397593753"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397594347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397594347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397595091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397595091"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397597862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397597862"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397598675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397598675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397599449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397599449"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397600183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397600183"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397603114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397603114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397603877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397603877"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397605120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397605120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397605574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397605574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397606578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397606578"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397607103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397607103"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397607737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397607737"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397608101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397608101"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397608724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397608724"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397611873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397611872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397612605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397612605"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397612838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397612838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397613371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397613371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397613564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397613564"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397614178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397614177"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397614871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397614870"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITANO"," userResponse":" MITANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397617548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397617548"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" ALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397618220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397618220"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397618550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397618549"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397619554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397619554"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHOVU"," userResponse":" UCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397620368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397620368"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397620602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397620602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397621125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397621125"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397622117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397622117"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397624571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397624570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397625183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397625182"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397625363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397625362"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397625945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397625944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397626394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397626394"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397626808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397626808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397627913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397627913"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397629143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397629142"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIISHIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397629746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397629746"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397630220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397630220"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397630986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397630986"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397631785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397631784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLISHA"," userResponse":" KUMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397634944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397634944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPACHA"," userResponse":" MAPACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397635578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397635578"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397635804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397635804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397636513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397636512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397637634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397637633"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397638780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397638780"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397638844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397638843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397639446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397639446"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397640251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397640250"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397643017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397643016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397644034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397644034"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEZALIWA"," userResponse":" WAMEZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397644544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397644543"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397644816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397644816"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397645104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397645103"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397647813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397647813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397648977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397648976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397649540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397649540"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397652469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397652468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397653143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397653143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397654805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397654805"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397655920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397655919"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397656736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397656732"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397657709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397657709"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAGA"," userResponse":" ALIAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397658403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397658403"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397659174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397659174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397659788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397659788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397660482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397660482"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397660727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397660727"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397661374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397661374"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397661858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397661857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397662872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397662871"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397665441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397665440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397666124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397666124"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397666334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397666334"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397667240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397667239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397667868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397667867"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397669391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397669391"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWOKOA"," userResponse":" WALIMWOKOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397670059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397670058"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397673458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397673458"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397673696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397673696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397674218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397674217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397674945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397674945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397675406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397675405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397675572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397675572"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397676108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397676108"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397677049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397677048"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397677997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397677997"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397678858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397678858"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOPI"," userResponse":" KOPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397679937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397679934"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEPI"," userResponse":" KEPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397680578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397680578"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397681345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397681345"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEJI"," userResponse":" KEJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397683972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397683971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397684936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397684936"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASIMBA"," userResponse":" WANASIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397685843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397685842"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397686080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397686079"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397686620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397686619"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397686836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397686836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397687254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397687253"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397687706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397687706"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397690447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397690447"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHISI"," userResponse":" WALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397690870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397690869"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" KIU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397691464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397691464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397692557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397692557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397695988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397695988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397696403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397696402"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397697205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397697205"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397697769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397697769"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397699072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397699072"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPENDA"," userResponse":" WALIWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397699675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397699675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397700162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397700162"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397700947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397700947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397701320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397701320"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397702205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397702205"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATUKUTU"," userResponse":" WATUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397705242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397705242"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397705818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397705817"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397706438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397706437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397706976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397706976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397709782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397709781"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397710686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397710685"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397711443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397711443"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFICHA"," userResponse":" KUFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397711930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397711930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397712008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397712008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d566248-c488-45fc-a084-39a08e5354b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFICHA"," userResponse":" KUFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397724352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397724352"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397724739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397724739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397724975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397724975"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397725296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397725295"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397725535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397725535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397729032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397729032"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397729340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397729340"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397730244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397730244"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397730668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397730668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397733685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397733685"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397733968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397733968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397734835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397734834"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397735502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397735501"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397736235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397736235"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397736558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397736558"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397736832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397736832"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397737153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397737153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397737432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397737432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397738035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397738034"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397738111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397738111"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 0c66d022-90d4-419c-a7d5-1e6243c5a50a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397747946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397747946"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397754445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397754445"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397760020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397760020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397765820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397765820"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397771083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397771083"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397776954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397776954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397782762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397782762"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397788958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397788958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397794718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397794717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397800337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397800337"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397810075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397810075"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397817047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397817046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 4565bb9b-bd83-49d6-a891-b38ae44d8a84"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397828879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397828879"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 94e72490-ba30-4f1d-b643-cdd7fb8eab61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397829105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397829104"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 94e72490-ba30-4f1d-b643-cdd7fb8eab61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397829189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397829188"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 94e72490-ba30-4f1d-b643-cdd7fb8eab61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397836426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397836426"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 94e72490-ba30-4f1d-b643-cdd7fb8eab61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397847444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397847444"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 94e72490-ba30-4f1d-b643-cdd7fb8eab61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397854409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397854409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 94e72490-ba30-4f1d-b643-cdd7fb8eab61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397865119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397865119"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397865611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397865611"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397865970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397865970"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397866733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397866732"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397867272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397867272"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397867755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397867755"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397870944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397870943"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397871567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397871567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397872270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397872270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397872454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397872454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397872897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397872897"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397873131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397873131"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397873625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397873625"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397874588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397874588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397878001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397877999"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" NAHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397878534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397878534"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONE"," userResponse":" TONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397878713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397878713"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397879377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397879376"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397880002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397880001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397880341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397880340"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397881164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397881163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINATOKA"," userResponse":" LINATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397881670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397881670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397882286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397882286"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nahitaji tone la maji hata kama linatoka kwenye jani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397885427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397885426"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397885934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397885933"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397886608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397886608"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMANDE"," userResponse":" UMANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397887347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397887346"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397888180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397888180"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hata umande ulikuwa umekauka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKAUKA"," userResponse":" UMEKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397891507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397891507"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," userResponse":" NISIPOKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397892200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397892200"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397893685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397893685"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" NITAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397894890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397894889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397895343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397895343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397896015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397896015"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisipokunywa maji nitakufa Siafu Mdogo alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397899081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397899079"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397899682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397899682"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" NIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397900139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397900139"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397900670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397900670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397901235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397901235"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAO"," userResponse":" AMBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397902099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397902099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397902538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397902537"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397902964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397902964"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwenye mto ambao nilisikia juu yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397906603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397906603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397908339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397908339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," userResponse":" UTAKUFAGILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397909105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397909104"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397909912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397909912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397910507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397910506"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397910972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397910972"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397911585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397911584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEKIMA"," userResponse":" HEKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397912813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397912812"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mto utakufagilia mbali panya mmoja mwenye hekima alimwonya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397915901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397915900"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397916433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397916433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397916983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397916983"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397917600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397917600"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397917791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397917791"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397918360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397918359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" KIU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397919281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397919280"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397922506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397922503"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" NITAKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397923364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397923364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397924134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397924134"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" SITIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397924771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397924771"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397925651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397925649"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa ikiwa sitikunywa maji yoyote."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397929174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397929174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397929904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397929903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397930652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397930651"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397931806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397931805"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397932434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397932434"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alienda kuutafuta mto..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397935412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397935412"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" KUPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397935889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397935889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397936502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397936499"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397937858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397937857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397938333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397938333"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397938731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397938730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397939648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397939648"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397940880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397940879"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kupita kwenye nyasi zilizokauka na kwenye matawi yaliyokauka..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOKAUKA"," userResponse":" YALIYOKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397943849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397943848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397944743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397944743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397945489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397945489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWIMBI"," userResponse":" MAWIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397945573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397945573"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397946080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397946080"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397947512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397947512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi aliposikia mawimbi ya mto yakinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKINGURUMA"," userResponse":" YAKINGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397950774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397950772"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397951307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397951306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397952307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397952307"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397952944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397952943"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397953855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397953854"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo alikunywa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397958018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397958018"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397958869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397958869"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397959812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397959812"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" KIASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397960010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397960009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397960580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397960580"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397961639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397961639"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUONA"," userResponse":" HAKUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397962051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397962051"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBI"," userResponse":" WIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397962704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397962704"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397963280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397963280"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahia sana kiasi cha kwamba hakuona wimbi kubwa likija."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIJA"," userResponse":" LIKIJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397966345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397966343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397967285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397967285"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJARIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397967949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397967948"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHIKA"," userResponse":" KUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397968467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397968466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397969110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397969110"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397970580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397970579"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOMPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIZOMPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397971555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397971555"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKIELEA"," userResponse":" ZIKIELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397974377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397974376"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397975491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397975491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAGILIWA"," userResponse":" ALIFAGILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397976307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397976307"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397976516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397976516"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397976986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397976986"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alifagiliwa mbali kwa maji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397979942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397979941"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397981005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397981004"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANISAIDIE"," userResponse":" ANISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397984474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397984473"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" NISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397985366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397985366"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nisaidie tafadhali."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397989301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397989301"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397990036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397990036"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDA"," userResponse":" PANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397990468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397990468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397991445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397991445"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIWA"," userResponse":" NJIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397992059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397992058"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" MWEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397992890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397992889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397993521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397993521"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397994146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397994145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397995197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397995196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," userResponse":" AMEMNYOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397995910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397995910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397996474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397996474"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397996969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397996969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548397997383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548397997383"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398016642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398016642"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398016740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398016740"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 3a1a3cb6-cab0-4c6b-b1e3-19145f05b8a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haraka panda juu Njiwa Mweupe alisema huku akiwa amemnyoshea tawi kwenye mdomo wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398028243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398028243"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398028692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398028692"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398029053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398029053"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398029807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398029806"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398030345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398030345"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398030827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398030826"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto katika msitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398034026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398034021"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398034510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398034509"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398034588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398034588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAFU"," userResponse":" SIAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398041670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398041670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398048865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398048864"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398055898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398055898"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398147979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398147979"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 65ae0c4b-97ca-4398-9fc6-f3e69c7dd9a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_19"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Siafu Mdogo hakuwa na maji kwa siku nyingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398148082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398148082"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ef108f70-5c3b-4987-9b93-33b3ee4c86ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398165181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398165181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee0cf51d-66b8-456b-848b-926c5fc0e345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398169468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398169468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee0cf51d-66b8-456b-848b-926c5fc0e345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398171040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398171040"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee0cf51d-66b8-456b-848b-926c5fc0e345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398172295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398172295"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee0cf51d-66b8-456b-848b-926c5fc0e345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398172409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398172409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" ee0cf51d-66b8-456b-848b-926c5fc0e345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398182476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398182476"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398185956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398185956"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398186932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398186932"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398187231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398187231"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398189834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398189834"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398190244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398190243"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398193066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398193065"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398197669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398197669"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398201913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398201912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398209170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398209169"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398242661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398242660"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398253140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398253139"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 818a4869-66ec-43b0-8024-641c8a55f28c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398263227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398263227"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a50105a3-c3c5-4e9c-ab90-e1d4767a2716"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398269146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398269145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a50105a3-c3c5-4e9c-ab90-e1d4767a2716"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398276493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398276493"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a50105a3-c3c5-4e9c-ab90-e1d4767a2716"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398288411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398288410"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a50105a3-c3c5-4e9c-ab90-e1d4767a2716"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398297780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398297780"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a50105a3-c3c5-4e9c-ab90-e1d4767a2716"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398312456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398312456"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a50105a3-c3c5-4e9c-ab90-e1d4767a2716"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398312541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398312541"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 727a197e-9e32-49b7-9ef5-6122536de086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398320032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398320030"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 727a197e-9e32-49b7-9ef5-6122536de086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398344477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398344477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398348559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398348558"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398350474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398350474"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398353137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398353137"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398354512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398354512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398357319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398357318"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398359896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398359896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398364259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398364259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398366688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398366688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398371959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398371959"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398372308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398372308"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398384451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398384451"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398385598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398385598"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398386330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398386329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398388260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398388260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398393673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398393673"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398400373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398400373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398404899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398404899"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398416043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398416042"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398417025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398417025"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398417692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398417692"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398422398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398422397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398427404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398427404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398432348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398432348"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398435078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398435078"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398435839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398435839"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398447604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398447603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" 7d91dc3f-d98f-4090-ace1-9eea79a5eda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_5v2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398591741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398591741"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398594147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398594147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398598834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398598834"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398600955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398600955"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398603187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398603187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398605334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398605333"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398608763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398608762"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398613536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398613535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398663514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398663514"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398663626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398663626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFAKA"," userResponse":" NAFAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398670938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398670938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" d36c250f-07aa-4d42-b403-75d2c882fb8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mwingine tunampa nafaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548398682041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548398682040"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_090649"," gameId":" a51a8a54-d2b0-4d19-9f23-f0545df0c4e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}